Hey.
おい
Well, what I asked everyone to gather today is
まあ今日みんなに集まってもらったのは、
It's something like no other,
他にもないあれなんだけど、
Well, I'm just a little, so don't get a little annoyed by yourself.
まあ 俺ちょっとさ、一人ちょっとムカつくのないで
Well, about that,
まあだからさ、そいつのことをさ、
I want everyone to do it.
みんなでさ、やっちゃってほしいんだよね
Well, she's a pretty cute girl, but there are a few things going on with her.
まあ結構かわいい女なんだけど、 まあ ちょっといろいろあって
Well, spring is here, so I thought I'd give it a little petting.
さ、 春立つからさ、 まあちょっとかわいがってあげようかなと
Well, I thought maybe I should take good care of it, but...
も さ、大事にしてあげようかなとも思ったんだけど、
I just can't forgive it, so it's not everyone's toy.
どうしても許せないから、ちょっとみんなのおもちゃじゃないけど
Well, from now on, I'll be a bit of a woman.
さ、 まあこれからちょっと女方としてさ、
I thought I'd put it to use.
使っていってやろうかなと思ったわけよ
So, what if I'm the one who's living now?
で、もしさ、今自分がさ、生女方はさ、
If you like it, is there anything you would like to do?
気に入るんだったらさ、 何かしたいこととかあったりする?
everyone.
みんな
So let's play one by one.
じゃあちょっと一人ずつ弾いていこうかな
Do you want to get a little deep?
ちょっとイラマしたいかな
Ah, Irama.
あ、イラマ
So go ahead and do your best, look sad.
じゃあ思いっきりやってさ、苦しい顔さ、
Let's do it.
させちゃおう
It's okay.
オッケーです
No, I licked it all over my body.
いやもう全身、至るところベロベロ舐め回して
That's nice.
いいねー
Lick it.
舐め回す
I want to lick it all over.
舐め回してやりたいっすね
Please.
頼むよ
I just want to be really good friends.
シンプルにめっちゃ仲良ししたいっすね
How many days have you saved today?
今日は何日貯めてきた?
Today, I've been saving up for a week.
今日はね、割り割りね、1週間貯めてきました
Aren't you going to get pregnant?
妊娠ちゃうんじゃないの?
If you get pregnant, I'll have you come again.
妊娠したらまたね、来てもらうからね
looking forward to it.
楽しみにしています
I want to lick it all over too.
俺も全身舐めたいな
Where do you want to lick?
どこ舐めたい?
I want to put a lot of chews on my face and stuff.
お顔とかにチューとかもいっぱいしたいな
Beloved.
ベロベロ
Oh, are you going to make it look like that?
あ、そんな感じにするの?
What was the story?
どういう話だったんですか?
I also had the full course.
僕もフルコースで
I want to lick her all over, make her horny, and finally have sex with her.
全身舐め回して、いらまして、最後仲出ししたいです
I want to have sex.
仲出ししたい
I want to do the full course.
フルコースでやりたいっすね
But that's okay.
でもいいよ
Because she's a girl.
女の子だからね
May I?
いいですか?
fun.
楽しみ
It's a competition between the two of us to see which one will do the erotic chewing.
2人でどっちがエロいチューするか勝負だね
Show me.
見せてくれよ
Show me, Chu.
見せてくれよ、チューはよ
How do you feel, Chu?
どんな感じですんの、チューは?
Ah, the type that closes its eyes.
ああ、目閉じるタイプ
After all, I like seeing women cry.
やっぱさ、女の泣き顔見るの好きだからさ
Disturb me until I cry.
泣くまでさ、かき乱して
Disturb.
かき乱す
I really want to do it.
むちゃくちゃやりたい
I want to do it so badly, while watching your crying face.
むちゃくちゃやりたいね、泣き顔見ながらさ
It's great to make out.
仲出しするの最高だよ
But I don't have to record it.
でも演録しなくていいから
Highest.
最高
No, is everyone feeling good?
いや、みんないい感じ?
I think the woman will come soon.
もうすぐ女来ると思うから
Let's have fun.
楽しんじゃおうか
It's okay, it's okay.
いいです、いいです
Well then, all of a sudden, even if you come like this, I'll fall in love with you.
じゃあ、いきなりさ、こんな来ても愛しまいちゃうからさ
I'm sure it'll only be once, but stay hidden over there.
きっと一回さ、あっちのほう隠れといて
It's okay, it's okay.
いいです、いいです
I'll take it without you.
いない手にするからよ
It's been a while.
久しぶりに
久しぶりです
The atmosphere has changed again.
なんかまた雰囲気変わったね
Is it clothes?
服ですか?
Clothes?
服?
Yeah.
うん
What, Ninghai today?
何、今日ニンハイなの?
Sex is good.
エッチいいじゃん
I like it, it goes well with many different outfits.
いいね、いろんな服装に合うね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
She's so cute, though.
そんな可愛いんだけどさ、
Actually, I'm a little irritated.
実 はちょっと、 僕ちょっとイライラしてます
No, the actor came last time, right?
いやさ、 前回さ、男優さん来たでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
Hey, at that time, after it was over...
ねえ、そのときにさ、 なんか、 終わったあとさ、
You didn't say anything about cleaning or anything like that.
そのなんかお掃除とかなんかさ、 なんか言ってなかったよね、
You did a lot of things.
やってたよね、いろいろ
yes.
はい
Yeah, did you do it with me?
そう、俺のときしたっけ?
i don't know.
知りません
I agree.
そうだね
Why, why, why.
なん、なんでなんでなんで
Before, I said,
なんか前は自分から、
I think it's too late, or maybe I can't realize it sooner.
遅 いというか、 もっと自分から早く気づけできないのかなと思
Because of that, I also, uh, get quite irritated.
ってる から、 俺も、 あの、結構イライラしちゃうから、
I feel like today too, I want to ask you something like, ``Hamidoi.''
なんか今日もちょっとね、 はみどいみたいな感じで聞きたいか
I can't help it, but today...
もし れないけど、 今日ちょっと、
I invited a friend, huh?
お友達呼んであげたから、 え?
In short, it's actually cuter,
短的に言うと、 本当はね、 もっと可愛いから、
I thought it would be more important, but
もっと大事にしていこうかなと思ったんだけど、
Of course I can't forgive either, so from now on...
さすがに俺も許せないから、 これからあの、
You are my, our, masturbator,
君 は、 俺の、 俺たちの、 オナホールとして、
As Ganga, I will let you live,
ガンガとして、 生きていってもらうから、
Today, as part of the travel exercise, I will take a moment.
今日はその旅行演習で、 一旦ちょっと、
Shall we all play together, including Croix Goss?
クロワゴスも含めて、 みんなで遊ぼうか
Everyone can come in.
みんな入っていっていいや
Want to try toys?
おもちゃをしてみる?
It's cute.
可愛いっすね
I can't forgive you either, as I said earlier.
俺も許せないからさ、さっき言ったけど、
You can do whatever you want with this guy.
好きにしていいから、こいつ
It's fun.
楽しいんだよ
It's a wonderful masturbator.
素晴らしいオナホールだ
Good luck?
よくね?
I can make such a cute masturbator though.
こんな可愛いオナホールできるけど
Ah, that's better.
あ、そっちのほうがいいよ
So cute.
めっちゃ可愛い
It smells good.
いい匂いするね
I don't want to chew on a masturbator.
オナホールにチューするってやだって
You really hate it, don't you?
めっちゃ嫌がってくるじゃないですか
I hate it
嫌が
That's what I'm saying.
って くる
air
気
That's good, this guy.
が いいよ、こいつ
It's a masturbator, so it's impossible.
オナホールなんだから、 無理だよ、
It's impossible.
無理だよ
Bad?
悪くね?
I mean, how many people do you think there are?
ってか、 何人いると思って
masturbator
オナホール
Because it's embarrassing to come here.
に 来てる時点で恥ずかしいから
It's too deep, oh
食い込みすぎた、お
forward.
前
She's so cute and so beautiful.
め っちゃチクビ可愛くて、 めっちゃ綺麗なんだけど
Don't hide it, don't hide it.
隠すなよ、隠すなよ
Anime love.
アニメ恋じゃん
Please eat it.
食べてくださいじゃん
I hope you all don't make me feel bad.
みんなで私のこと気持ち悪くしてくれないだろ
Please do me a favor.
お願いしろよ
Don't do it too much, you might hurt yourself.
あんまりね、するとね、 怪我させちゃうかもしれないからね
If you get hurt, you'll become addicted.
怪我したら中毒になっちゃうから
Because it's a big deal.
せっかくだから
About pants.
パンツくらい
Quickly take off your pants.
早く脱げよ、パンツは
Take it off, take it off quickly.
脱げ早く脱げよ
Make me take it off?
脱げさせる?
Show me your masturbator, masturbator.
オナホール見せてくれよ、オナホール
Show me your masturbation, masturbation.
オ ナホール見せてよ、オナホール
Oh, the onahole came out.
おっ、出てきたオナホール
oh.
おー
My pants come off.
パンツ抜ける
Isn't something damp?
何か湿ってんじゃねーの?
This is it, this.
これなんだよ、これ
Isn't it damp?
湿ってんじゃねーの?
I'm embarrassed to see this.
これ見られるの恥ずかしいから
People who want this, people who want this.
これ欲しい人、欲しい人
Don't you like it?
好きじゃねーか
After all, there is time for real things.
やっぱ本物の時間もあるから
What are you doing?
何してんの?
My stomach is small.
お腹ちっちゃいな
Oh, you're bothering me.
お ー、手邪魔だよ
Can I explain it myself?
自分で説明していい?
What kind of onahole is that?
どんなオナホールじゃねーか
What is this?
これ何?
Where is this?
ここどこ?
what?
何?
I can't hear you.
聞こえねーよ
This looks like a bean.
豆みたいなんだよ、これ
I don't understand.
分 かんない
Why are you alive?
なんで生きてんだ?
Let me tell you three things.
教えてやれよ、3点を
It's a small and comfortable masturbator.
ちっちゃめで気持ちいいオナホールですって
I'm here.
しま いますって
Is it small?
ちっちゃむの?
That's right.
そうなんだよ
I have to try it.
使ってみないと
Well, I'll try to taste it later.
じゃあ後でちょっとね、ゆっくり味わってみる
She's a masturbation princess.
オナホのお姫様だ
It's out, it's out.
出た、出た
That's amazing.
すげーな
It's completely visible.
丸見えだよ
Try expanding it yourself.
自分で広げてみて
With both hands.
両手で
If you can't adjust it, you can't stop.
調整できないとやめられないからさ
If you don't hurry, it won't be over.
早くしないと終わらないから
More firmly.
もっともっとしっかり
Don't spread it out any further.
もっとガガっと広げない
I want to hear what you have to say right now.
すぐ言うこと聞きたい
Not too shameless.
恥知らずすぎないから
cute.
かわいい
Whether you agree or not, I want to see what you do today.
よろすかどうか、今日のお前の行いしたいから
do my best.
頑張る
Two people came?
2人来た?
Don't look.
見ないでー
見 ないでー
While talking more.
もっと話しながら
amazing.
すごい
I got 4 pieces.
4本入っちゃった
Awesome.
すげー
But it's tough, that's for sure.
でもきついね、確かに
It might be tough.
きついかも
Why check, brother?
チェックなんで、お兄さん?
I'm not trying to be your older brother.
お兄さんになってつもりないんだけど
It's my uncle.
おじさんだよ
It feels better to open your hand more and put it in.
もっと手が開いて入れたほうが気持ちいい
Before anyone puts their dick in,
誰がさ、みんなチンコ入れる前にさ、
The umbrella is really narrow, just like the product information said earlier.
本当に狭いかさ、さっきの商品案内通りかさ、
Let's check it out.
確かめようよ
nice.
いい ね
Which feels better, the effort you put in earlier?
さっきの手間とどっちが気持ちいいんだ?
I have no feelings.
気持ちがない
What are you saying?
なんてこと言うんだ
Don't get hurt.
傷つくな
I'll go next time.
次行くぞ
You're the third person.
お前3番3人目
It's a shame.
惜しくなっちゃった
Please stop it.
やめてくださーい
too good to waste.
もったいない
It sure feels good.
確かに気持ちよさそうではあるね
Gome
ごめ
Nah, that's it.
んな さい
I didn't say let's go with the girl from earlier.
さっきの女の子しようって言ってない
sorry.
ごめんなさい
Are you watching?
見してるか?
The face is close.
顔近い
Good.
よいしょ
Oh, that's cute.
あら、かわいい
I'm expanding it myself.
自分で広げてる
Your face is cute.
かわいいよ顔が
You can do it.
できるだろ
Expand it further.
も っと広げな
It's so slimy that I can't grab it.
ぬるぬるで掴めないんだ
Can't you?
できないのか
Then I'll spread it out.
じゃあ広げてやるよ
You're peace.
お前はピースしてる
I'm doing it in pieces.
ピースでしてる
No way.
いやー
please.
お願い
No way.
だめー
no
いや
ー.
ー
I'm so happy.
嬉 しいね
I'm not happy.
嬉しくない
It's so small.
すげー狭いな
Anyone.
誰だって
You can lick me anytime.
いつでも舐めていいよ
You can lick it.
舐 めていいよ
舐めていいよ
Hey, you.
いねぇかお前
I just took it out.
さっき出しただけ
What do you want?
どうしてほしいの?
one
一
Yes, it's not cold though.
応 寒くないんだけど
Good, good, good.
いいよいいよ
Stand upright.
立て立て立て
It's difficult to do there.
そこじゃやりにくいから
Let's sit down on our knees.
膝ついて座ろう
Lick it yourself.
自分で舐める
Make yourself feel good.
気持ちよくして
It looks so delicious.
すっげーうまそう
I can't believe how good it was.
せっきょんなに良かったと思えない
You can still go.
まだいけるだろ
Hey, use your hands.
おい、手使うの
I use my hands.
手 使うの
You can go.
いけるだろ
Thank you for using it properly.
ちゃんと使ってくれて
I am me.
俺は俺
There are 6 pieces for each person, so I'll go ahead and do it all.
一人一人6個あるから、全員俺行ってちゃんと
thank you.
ありがとうございます
yes.
はい
First, lick the whole thing before adding it.
まずは、加える前に全体舐めて
Lick it, lick it.
舐めて舐めて
Lick, lick.
舐 めて 舐めて
I told her I could add it, and then I added it.
加えていいよって言ってから加えて
Oh, you're so good at it.
ああ、上手上手
Try to go as deep as you can.
なるべく奥まで頑張ってね
On the other hand, not with no hands, but with both hands.
逆 にノーハンドじゃなくて、両手使ってしごきながら
Fill it with slobber and add it while squeezing.
よだりいっぱいにしてしごきながら加えて
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
そうそうそうそう
You're good at it.
上手だね
dangerous.
あぶない
Why that combination?
なんでそのコンビネーション
Immediately, something felt off.
すぐになんか、すっっている
thank you.
ありがとうございます
It's a toy.
おもちゃなんだからな
You'll know when I bring it to you.
持ってあげたら分かってるよ
It's cute how you're acting so cute.
せいざしてるの可愛いね
People shoot themselves in the head.
人間は頭を撃ちます
It's fun to sway your hips.
腰を揺れるのが面白いです
Gohoko is standing.
五帆子が立っています
I think there are still two.
まだ2人いると思います
My body is fast.
体が早いです
It hurts.
痛いです
It cannot be inflated.
膨らむことはできません
It's not over yet.
まだ 終わりです
I'll still do it first.
まだ最初にやります
Lick the sign.
看板を舐めます
yes.
はい
It's the last one.
最後です
Oh, he's not coming here.
あ、こっち来ないよ
Here it is because it's interesting.
面白いからこっちで
It's definitely a style.
確かにスタイルよ
good
いい
Hey, blood vessels are amazing.
ね、 血管すごい
It feels like you're working hard.
頑張ってる感じがですね
cute.
かわいい
Chibochiboi.
ちぼちぼいって
picture,
え、
I also rode a little and it hurt a lot.
俺 もちょっと乗ってすっごい痛いの
Stretch your head a little, stretch it out.
ちょっと頭伸ばして、伸ばして
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうだね
It seems like it would fit better that way.
その向きの方が入りそうだね
It's disgusting.
気持ち悪いわ
Your body is floating in the center.
中央に浮いてるじゃん、体
It went below.
下回ったわ
Floating.
浮いていく
It's being combed out.
くし出されてるじゃん
You don't realize it, do you?
気づいてないんじゃないの?
My pussy is being used.
マンコ使われてる
I'm aware.
気づいてる
As expected, it's pitch black.
さすがに真っ黒
sorry.
ごめんなさい
Please push your hand in.
手を押し込んでください
Stick your feet out.
足を突き出してください
Isn't it flying?
飛んでいないですか?
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
Welcome back.
おかえり
Is it a women's hall?
女ホールだろ?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's a women's hall.
女ホールですって
I'll put my cock in it, and that's it.
チンポ入れてやるから、そした
and others.
ら
It opens even if you hold it by hand.
手 を持っても開いてますよ
Senma.
せんま
I wanted to grow my hair while brushing it.
髪をきしながらふやさせたかったんだよね
Full body female hall.
全身女ホール
Cue
キ ュ
Tikuri.
ーテ ィクリが
Do you like the back?
奥が好きなのか?
I don't like the back.
奥好きじゃない
He says he likes the interior.
奥好きだって
fun.
楽しみ
You can wrap your cuticle around the cock.
キューティクリはチンポに絡みつけていいですよ
Do you know what's going on?
何されてるか分かってるのか?
It's too much of a toy, isn't it?
おもちゃすぎるでしょ
Isn't it a real toy?
リアルおもちゃじゃないか?
sorry.
ごめんなさい
Go
い け
Go.
What a shame, this stomach.
あばれんな、このお腹
sorry.
ごめんなさい
Shall I let my hair out too?
髪も出しちゃおうか
I also let out my hair.
髪も出しちゃって
Where will you finish it?
ど んなところで仕上げるんだね
Shall I let my hair out too?
髪も出しちゃおうか
good?
いい?
I also let out my hair.
髪も出しちゃって
It's because I'm hungry.
お腹だからね
I can't refuse.
拒否とかできない
I cried because it felt so good.
気持ちよすいって泣いちゃった
You cried.
泣いたじゃん
I must have cried.
泣いちゃったんじゃん
It's smooth.
つりつるやね
It's true.
本当だ
It's pretty tight.
結構きついね
It feels good.
気持ちいいよね
It feels so natural.
天然通り気持ちいいね
It feels good and makes me feel sick.
気持ちよくて気持ち悪くしてるね
amazing.
すごい
amazing?
すごい?
It feels amazing.
気持ちすごい
I'll give you a cock later.
あとでチンポするからね
Remember that.
覚えとけよ
Who had what kind of dick?
誰がどんなチンポだったか
cute.
かわいい
There's still some chincha.
まだチンチャあるからね
Are you dating?
お前付き合ってんのかな?
My dad let me use this.
父さんこんなの使わせてくれて
Good, good, good.
いいよいいよ
Because it belongs to everyone.
みんなのものだからね
Use it as you like.
好きに使えな
When I take my cock out, the bottom starts to stretch.
チンポ出したら下が伸びてくるようになってる
You like it.
好きなんだね
hey.
ね
I love it.
大 好きです
It feels good, it feels good.
気持ちいい気持ちいい
amazing.
すごい
A candy that seems to like dicks.
チンポ好きそうな飴が
hey.
ね
You love cock.
チンポ大好きなんだね
You've finally started to speak your mind.
やっと本音言うようになったね
The recommended type for masturbation has arrived.
オナホにおすすめのタイプが来ました
Does it feel good to type it in?
タイプで入れるのが気持ちいいか
Did everyone like it?
みんな気に入ったか?
I put it in.
俺入れました
Onahole, come here.
オナホこっち来いよ
Fully automatic masturbation.
全自動オナホ
Go quickly.
早く行け
Forward.
前向け
No way.
いやー
Stop it.
や めて
Stop.
や め
Ani
あに
Yeah.
ゃ
I said, “Ah!”
あ にゃって言ったわ
Reverse and reverse.
反対になって逆に
Because it was reversed.
逆にしたから
Please take a look at it carefully.
せっかくだからそっと見ろ
Everyone is watching.
みんな見てる
Not like a lover.
恋人風じゃなくて
Are you dating?
付き合ってるのか?
Say it quickly.
早く言えよ
Are you okay.
大丈夫
A man with a big waist?
腰大丈夫?
Really.
本当に
We don't get along.
仲良くしてません
結
Structure: Certainly.
構 確かに
It's a good masturbator.
いいオナホです
It's not broken until you use it.
使うまで壊れてないね
Oh naho.
オ ナホ
charge
押
vinegar?
す?
Press.
押 します
Good girl?
いい子?
I'm catching it.
捕まえてる
nice.
いいね
It looks like a shrimp.
エビみたいになってる
If you can hear it, it's onahoika.
聞こえたらオナホイカだぞ
it hurts.
痛い
緊張
Not yet.
まだまだ
Get it out from below.
下から出せよ
People who can't put it out will be in trouble.
出せん人は困るからよ
what?
何?
There are people in there.
人入ってます
From the hand that lets me hold your dick.
ちんこ握らせてくれの手から
Let's take a picture as a souvenir.
記念に撮っちゃおう
I want to teach a masturbator about being moody,
オナホに気むずりを教えてあげたいんだけど、
good?
いい?
Please make love to me.
仲出ししてくださいって
Please make out.
仲出ししてください
Everyone, it's me.
みなさん私で
Everyone please make me feel better.
みなさん私で気持ちよくなってください
You can all leave.
みんな出していっちゃっていいよ
Now
さっ
What lines did you teach?
き 教えたセリフは?
Please make out.
仲出ししてください
Do you know what's coming out?
出てんのわかるか?
Don't move, don't move.
動くな動くな
Hold on, hold on.
踏ん張って踏ん張って
Show your fins.
ひれ出せよ
joke.
冗談
Yes, first shot.
はい、一発目
I think I'll let you pilot it for a bit.
ちょっと操縦してもらおうかな、せっかくだから
Thank you for the first shot.
一発目ありがとうございました
All at once.
一気にして
Thank you for the first shot.
一発目ありがとうございました
We'll do it together.
一緒にします
yes.
はい
I can't.
できない
Everyone will come out.
み んな出していってくれるから
please.
お願いします
I'll take it out.
出してやるよ
Let's go.
行くぞ
Well, I guess I'll give it another shot.
じゃあ、もう一発で出してもらおうかな
please.
お願いします
Go, go, go.
行く行く
Lover Jim is here, lover Jim.
恋人ジム来たよ、恋人ジム
Don't just let me out again, please make me pregnant.
また出してくださいじゃなくて、妊娠させてください
One more time.
もう一回
Baby, one more time.
赤ちゃん、もう一回ですって
I don't feel like taking a break.
休む気もないからね
I'll call you when we get horny.
俺らがムラムラしたら呼ぶからね
Really come.
ほんとに来いよ
If you say it's sweet, he'll do it more.
甘いよって言ってると、もっとやっちゃうよ
From now on, I will do my best as Onaho.
これからおなほとして、頑張りますって
nice.
いい ね
Let's do our best.
頑張ろうな
頑張ろう
Let's do our best.